Guide to the Stanford University, Faculty Affairs Office, Affirmative Action Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Faculty Affairs Office, Affirmative Action records
1979-2000
SC1014
Stanford University. Faculty Affairs Office.
10.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Materials were transferred from the Faculty Affairs Office, 2010.
Information about Access
Access: materials are not open to research use.
Scope and Contents note
Collection contains plans, reports, and other records pertaining to affirmative action in regard to Stanford faculty.
Collection Contents
- Records, 1979-2000; Accession ARCH-2010-141
  - Faculty AA (Affirmative Action), 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty AA, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - OFCCP (Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs) AA Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - OFCCP AA Plan, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AA Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty AA (Early 1990's), Circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Faculty AA (Early 1990's), Circa 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Minority Issues, 1989 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AA Plan, 1999 March (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - MWDD (Minority & Women Doctoral Directories VI), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - MWDD (VII), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - MWDD (VI), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - MWDD (VII), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AA Plan (Binder 1, Set #10), 1999 March (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - AA Plan (Binder 1, Set #8), 1999 March (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AA Plan (Binder 2, Audit), 1999 March (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - School Magna Cartas (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Faculty AA Report, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - OFCCP Semi-Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - AA Brochures, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mid-year AA Report - Staff, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - AA Plan (Binder 2, Audit), 1999 March (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AA Plan (Binder 3), 1999 March (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - AA Plan (Binder 3), 1999 March (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty AA Report, 1982 Sep 1-1983 Aug 31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Report of the Human Task Force Hiring Senior Women, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Report of the Human Task Force Hiring Senior Women, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Report of the Human Task Force Hiring Senior Women, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - AA - Faculty, 1976-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AA - H&S, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Human Task Force Hiring Senior Women, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Human Task Force Hiring Senior Women (Binder 2), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Report of the Provost's Task Force on Women Faculty in Social Sciences/Related Fields, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Faculty AA, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Report for the Human Task Force on Faculty Women Sceinces, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Report for the Human Task Force on Faculty Women Sceinces, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Analysis of Faculty AA, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Faculty AA, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Utilization Analysis, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Report of the Provost's Task Force on Women Faculty in Social Sciences/Related Fields, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Report of the Provost's Task Force on Women Faculty in Social Sciences/Related Fields, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Report of the Provost's Task Force on Women Faculty in Social Sciences/Related Fields, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Telecommunications IX Court Cases B. VS. AT&T (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - AA (Early 1990's), circa 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - PAG (Policy and Governance) Committee on Recruitment and Retention of Women Faculty (Minute Readings) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Provost's Task Force on Women Faculty in Sciences, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - FAA Report, 1981 Sep 1-1982 Sep 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - FAA Report, 1982 Oct 1-1983 Sep 30 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - AA and Faculty Hiring Process, 1970-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - AA Handbook for Faculty, Staff and Academic Staff, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - AA Report, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Faculty AA Report Instructions (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cares of University - 5 Year Report, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Self Study (Multiracial University Communities), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Annual Review Panel (Multiracial University Communities), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Self Study (Multiracial University Communities), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Harvard AA Plan, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Harvard AA Plan, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Final Report of University Committee on Minority Issues (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - CIC Directory, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - CIC Directory, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Dartmouth College AA Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Report of Medical School Committee on Professoriate, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Medical Staff Bylaws/Rules and Regulations of Stanford University Hospital, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)